https://www.afterglowskincare.ca/privacy-policy/

Eczema
Hyperhidrosis (Sweating)
Contact
Helping You Look & Feel More Radiant & EnergizedSchedule Your Consultation
Afterglow Physician Directed Medical Aesthetics
2609 Westview Dr. #104
North Vancouver, British Columbia V7N 4M2
Phone: (604) 980-3993
Monday–Friday: 9 a.m.–5 p.m.Saturday: 9 a.m.–1 p.m.
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Our Policy for Protecting Your Online Privacy
This website uses Google Analytics to help analyze how users use the site. The tool uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors’ use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity.
Privacy of Collected Data
We will never (and will not allow any third party to) use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any Personally Identifiable Information (PII) of visitors to our site. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Neither we nor Google will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any Personally Identifiable Information from any source, unless you explicitly submit that information via a fill-in form on our website.
Information to opt out of Google Analytics
Information About Remarketing
This website uses Google remarketing to advertise online using text or image ads on the Google Display Network. Remarketing is a feature that lets us reach people who have previously visited our site, and show them relevant ads when they visit other sites on the Google Display Network.
For websites using remarketing, a third-party DoubleClick cookie is used to enable remarketing for products like AdWords on the Google Display Network. When someone visits our website, a few lines of code will drop an anonymous browser cookie. This cookie is a small file that stores information. The cookie will store the site visit, but does not store any sensitive information, such as visitor name, address or any other piece of information that might personally identify the visitor. The cookie will be enabled for a set period of time, such as 30 or 60 days, at which time, the cookie expires.
What is the Google Display Network?
A group of more than a million websites, videos, and apps where ads can appear. Sites in this network have partnered with Google to show relevant AdWords ads.
Remarketing Restrictions
Our website will never:
run remarketing ads that collect Personally Identifiable Information (PII)
create a remarketing list or ad text that specifically targets users in ways that are outlined as “prohibited” by Google
Opting out of Remarketing
Visitors may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Ads Preference Manager. Visitors may opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.
Back to Top
Share
Tweet
Pin
Follow
Contact
Home
About
Eczema
Hyperhidrosis (Sweating)
Facial Asymmetry
Facial Spider Veins
Melasma
Psoriasis
Scars
Skin Cancer
Unwanted Fat
Unwanted Hair
September 2005
COVID-19 UPDATE:
Afterglow is OPEN and ready to welcome women and men seeking the best in aesthetic care. We've expanded and redecorated our practice and have adopted special safety precautions in the wake of the pandemic. This includes cleaning and disinfecting rooms and workstations throughout the day to help all of our patients and staff remain healthy. We have closed our Ambleside location, but the newly expanded Afterglow—less than 7 km away—is ready to accommodate Ambleside patients. We look forward to seeing you soon!
